<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Meteora</string>
    <string name="wrong_password">Password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="wrong_username">Username is incorrect</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="exit">EXIT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "\nIf this description will not answer your question, contact us via email: the button in the right will redirect you.\n\n"

        "LOGIN\n"
        "Open the application. The authentification credentials are the ones given from the coordinating"
        "team from Earth - the username is the unique id given at the beginning of the mission. In "
        "case of login problems or forgetting the login data, please contact the coordinating center "
        "manually from the spaceship. \n\n"

        "START CONVERSATION\n"
        "If you want to start a new conversation the three dot menu from the right-upper corner will"
        "redirect you to a list of persons including the team members from spaceship, the coordination team "
        "from Earth responsible for the mission and other people directly involved in the mission. "
        "When you choose a person from the list a new conversation screen will appear.\n"
        "If you already started a conversation with a person you can search and reopen it using the "
        "search menu bar. Type the username of the person you want to chat with, like "Mona" or search"
        "by date like 12.02.2017(DD.MM.YYYY).\n\n"

        "CHANGE PASSWORD\n"
        "Change password submenu can be accessed from the three-dot menu option "Setttings". In order to get "
        "your password changed retype twice the actual password and enter the new password twice. The password "
        "must contain at least 10 characters including 2 digits. \n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test">Test</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">Help</string>
    <string name="title_activity_change_password">ChangePassword</string>
    <string name="old_not_the_same">The old passwords are not the same</string>
    <string name="new_not_the_same">The new passwords are not the same</string>
    <string name="pass_changed">Password changed!</string>
    <string name="input_placeholder">Write a message</string>
</resources>
